ILGWU. National War Labor Board case files, 5780/085
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
ILGWU. National War Labor Board case files
1936-1946.
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union
5780/085
10 cubic feet
10 linear feet
Case files
Case files include arbitration notes, correspondence, Cotton Garment Industry Application for Wage Adjustments, legal documents, N.W.L.B. application for approval of wage or salary rate adjustment or schedule, notes, and payroll summaries covering the period 1936-1946.
5492855
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff
Date completed:
2003
EAD encoding:
Casey Westerman, 2003Cheryl Beredo, July 2011
Biographical / Historical
The International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union was founded in New York City in 1900 by mostly Socialist immigrant workers who sought to unite the various crafts in the growing women's garment industry. The union soon reflected changes in the sector and rapidly organized thousands of unskilled and semi-skilled women, mostly Jewish and Italian young immigrants. Exemplifying the "new unionism," the ILGWU led two of the most widespread and best-known industrial strikes of the early Twentieth Century: the shirtwaist makers' strike of 1909 in New York City and the cloak makers' strike of 1910 in Chicago. The union also tried to adapt to the fragmented and unstable nature of the industry. It adopted the "protocol of peace," a system of industrial relations that attempted to ensure stability and limit strikes and production disruption by providing for an arbitration system to resolve disputes.
The ILGWU exemplified the European-style social unionism of its founding members. They pursued bread and butter issues but provided educational opportunities, benefits, and social programs to union members as well. In 1919, the ILGWU became the first American union to negotiate an unemployment compensation fund that was contributed to by its employers. The ILGWU also pioneered in the establishment of an extremely progressive health care program for its members which included not only regional Union Health Centers but also a resort for union workers, known as Unity House. The Union also had an imaginative and pioneering Education Department which not only trained workers in traditional union techniques, but provided courses in citizenship and the English language.
David Dubinsky, an immigrant from Belarus who came to the US in 1911, provided strong leadership that led to unprecedented growth in the union during his presidency from 1932 to 1966. He led the union through successful internal anti-communist struggles, built on the ascendancy of industrial unionism by encouraging the formation of the Committee for Industrial Organization, and helped the union become an important political force in New York City and state politics, and in the national Democratic Party and Liberal Party as well.
In the period following the Second World War, the union suffered a decline in membership as manufacturers avoided unionization and took advantage of less expensive labor by moving shops from the urban centers in the northeast to the south, and later abroad. The ethnic and racial character of the ILGWU also changed as European immigrants were supplanted by Asians, Latin Americans, African- Americans, and immigrants from the Caribbean.
In July 1995 the ILGWU merged with the Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union (ACTWU) at a joint convention, forming UNITE (Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees). At the time the new union had a membership of about 250,000 in the United States, Canada, and Puerto Rico.
Scope and Contents
Case files include arbitration notes, correspondence, Cotton Garment Industry Application for Wage Adjustments, legal documents, N.W.L.B. application for approval of wage or salary rate adjustment or schedule, notes, and payroll summaries covering the period 1936-1946.
Conditions Governing Access
The ILGWU Records, except for publications and materials produced for publication, are restricted. Materials created prior to twenty years from the current date are open to researchers only with prior written permission from the Director of the Kheel Center; materials created during the past twenty-years are closed; the minutes of the General Executive Board are closed. For more information contact the Kheel Center.
Related Materials
5780. ILGWU records
5780/075. ILGWU. Collective Bargaining Agreements
5780/075mf. ILGWU. Collective Bargaining Agreements. Microfilm
5780/145. ILGWU. Association Agreements. Out-of-Business Contracts
5780/146. ILGWU. Master Agreements. Out-of-Business Contracts
5780/147. ILGWU. Independents. Out-of-Business Contracts
5780/158. ILGWU. Out-of-Business Contracts
5780/191. ILGWU. Association Contracts
5780/202. ILGWU. Operations Department. Collective Bargaining Agreements
General
"Permanent deposit"
Women's clothing industry -- United States; Clothing workers -- Labor unions -- United States; Clothing workers -- United States; Industrial relations -- United States; Wages -- Cost-of-living adjustments; United States. National War Labor Board (1942-1945)
5492855
- Abercrombie and Fitch. NWLB Case no.415, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Ace Manufacturing Corporation. NWLB Case no.13, 1942-1945 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Ace Manufacturing Corporation. NWLB Case no.433, 1942-1945 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  Scope and Contents
  See also NWLB Case no.13 and NWLB Case no.133
- Ace Manufacturing Corporation. NWLB Case no.133, 1942-1945 (Box 1, Folder 3a)
- Richard Alan Button. NWLB Case no.305, 1942-1944 (Box 1, Folder 3b)
- Alice in Wonderland Frocks Company. NWLB Case no.57, 1941-1944 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Alice in Wonderland Frocks Company. NWLB Case no.280, 1941-1944 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- All American Dress. NWLB Case no.399, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Aller Dress Company. NWLB Case no.456a, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  See also NWLB Case no.197
- Anderson Brothers. NWLB Case no.355, 1943-1945 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Anthony Allegro. NWLB Case no.65, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Appalachian Mills Company. NWLB Case no.33, 1942-1943 (Box 1, Folder 9a)
- Appomatox Garment. NWLB Case no.314, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Artu Undergarment Company. NWLB Case no.477, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Astoria Dress. NWLB Case no.308, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Baker Manufacturing Company. NWLB Case no.11, 1942-1943 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  See also NWLB Case no.171
- Baker Manufacturing Company. NWLB Case no.11, 1942-1943 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Baltimore Cutters - Cotton Garment. NWLB Case no.356, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Barbara Costume. NWLB Case no.302, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Barbizon Corporation. NWLB Case no.111, 1943-1945 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Barbizon Corporation. NWLB Case no.153, 1943-1945 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Barbizon Corporation. NWLB Case no.307, 1943-1945 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  See also NWLB Case no.111 and NWLB Case no.153
- Barbizon Corporation. NWLB Case no.423, 1943-1945 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  See also NWLB Case no.111, NWLB Case no.153, NWLB Case no.307
- Barbizon Corporation. NWLB Case no.440, 1943-1945 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  See also NWLB Case no.111, NWLB Case no.153, NWLB Case no.307, NWLB Case no.423
- Barson and Bishop. NWLB Case no.420, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 21a)
- Baumel Dress Company. NWLB Case no.53, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 21b)
- Belle Knitting Company. NWLB Case no.124, 1942-1945 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  See also NWLB Case no.162
- Belle Knitting Company. NWLB Case no.162, 1942-1945 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  See also NWLB Case no.124 and NWLB Case no.359
- Belle Knitting Company. NWLB Case no.359, 1942-1945 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  See also NWLB Case no.124 and NWLB Case no.162
- Belle Knitting Company. NWLB Case no.424, 1942-1945 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  See also NWLB Case no.124, NWLB Case no.162, NWLB Case no.359
- Bellmore Dress. NWLB Case no.51, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Louis Bendet Company. NWLB Case no.1, 1943-1944 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Louis Bendet Company. NWLB Case no.191, 1943-1944 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Louis Bendet Company. NWLB Case no.311, 1943-1944 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  See also NWLB Case no.1 and NWLB Case no.191
- Bennett Textile Company, Inc. NWLB Case no.443, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Bennington Mills. NWLB Case no.340, 1944-1945 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  See also NWLB Case no.151
- Bennington Mills. NWLB Case no.151, 1944-1945 (Box 1, Folder 31a)
- Bennington Mills. NWLB Case no.466, 1944-1945 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  See also NWLB Case no.151 and NWLB Case no.340
- Bergdorf Goodman. NWLB Case no.270, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  See also NWLB Case no.210
- Berkshire Mills, Inc. NWLB Case no.282, 1942-1945 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  See also NWLB Case no.23
- Berkshire Mills, Inc. NWLB Case no.23, 1942-1945 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Berkshire Tent Company. NWLB Case no.373, 1943-1944 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  See also NWLB Case no.23 and NWLB Case no.282
- Berkshire Tent Company. NWLB Case no.497, 1943-1944 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  See also NWLB Case no.23, NWLB Case no.282, NWLB Case no.373
- A. Bernstein. NWLB Case no.453, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 38)
- M. M. Bernstein and Sons. NWLB Case no.16, 1943-1946 (Box 1, Folder 39)
- M. M. Bernstein and Sons. NWLB Case no.188, 1943-1946 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  See also NWLB Case no.16
- M. M. Bernstein and Sons. NWLB Case no.498, 1943-1946 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  See also NWLB Case no.16, NWLB Case no.188, NWLB Case no.337
- M. M. Bernstein and Sons. NWLB Case no.337, 1943-1946 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  See also NWLB Case no.16 and NWLB Case no.188
- Best Maid Apparel Company. NWLB Case no.473, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 43)
- Better Made Sportswear Company. NWLB Case no.130, 1943-1944 (Box 1, Folder 44)
- Better Made Sportswear Company. NWLB Case no.324, 1943-1944 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  See also NWLB Case no.130
- Betty Maid. NWLB Case no.32, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 46)
- Betty Maid. NWLB Case no.258, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  See also NWLB Case no.32
- Biberman Brothers. NWLB Case no.465, 1943-1945 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  See also NWLB Case no.43 and NWLB Case no.384
- Biberman Brothers. NWLB Case no.384, 1943-1945 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  See also NWLB Case no.43
- Biberman Brothers. NWLB Case no.43, 1943-1945 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  See also NWLB Case no.384 and NWLB Case no.465
- Bleier Brothers. NWLB Case no.412, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 51)
- Blossom Products Corporation. NWLB Case no.389, 1943-1945 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  See also NWLB Case no.147
- Blossom Products Corporation. NWLB Case no.147, 1943-1945 (Box 1, Folder 53)
- Blossom Products Corporation. NWLB Case no.408, 1943-1945 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  See also NWLB Case no.147 and NWLB Case no.389
- H. Bomze and Brothers. NWLB Case no.463, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 55)
- H. Bomze Dress Company. NWLB Case no.462, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 56)
- Bonkosky Brothers. NWLB Case no.118, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 57)
- Borgenicht and Spiro, Inc. NWLB Case no.68, 1943-1944 (Box 1, Folder 58)
- Borgenicht and Spiro, Inc. NWLB Case no.245, 1943-1944 (Box 1, Folder 59)
  See also NWLB Case no.68
- Borgenicht and Spiro, Inc. NWLB Case no.293, 1943-1944 (Box 1, Folder 60)
  See also NWLB Case no.68 and NWLB Case no.245
- Borgenicht and Spiro, Inc. NWLB Case no.321, 1943-1944 (Box 1, Folder 61)
  See also NWLB Case no.68, NWLB Case no.245, NWLB Case no.293
- Boston Joint Board Dress. NWLB Case no.288, 1943-1944 (Box 1, Folder 62)
- Boulevard Frocks, Inc. NWLB Case no.39, 1943-1944 (Box 1, Folder 63)
- Boulevard Frocks, Inc. NWLB Case no.238, 1943-1944 (Box 1, Folder 64)
  See also NWLB Case no.39
- Branch Manufacturing Company. NWLB Case no.75, 1943-1944 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Branch Manufacturing Company. NWLB Case no.213a, 1943-1944 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  See also NWLB Case no.75
- A. L. Brand and Brand Brothers. NWLB Case no.169, NWLB Case no.170, 1943 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- L. Brodsky. NWLB Case no.370, 1944-1945 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Brookemeade Sportswear, Inc. NWLB Case no.69, 1941-1944 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Camlin Fashions. NWLB Case no.252, 1944 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Carr Manufacturing Company. NWLB Case no.246-A, 1944 (Box 2, Folder 6a)
  See also Seven Texas Firms NWLB Case no.246
- Celluplastics Corporation. NWLB Case no.139, 1943-1944 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Celluplastics Corporation. NWLB Case no.263, 1943-1944 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Central Dress Company. NWLB Case no.109, 1943 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Charis Corporation. NWLB Case no.383, 1945 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  See also NWLB Case no.17
- Charis Corporation. NWLB Case no.41, 1945 (Box 2, Folder 10a)
- Charmese Foundations. NWLB Case no.427, 1945 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Chicago Dress. NWLB Case no.341, 1944-1945 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Children's Wear. NWLB Case no.194, 1943-1944 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Chique Creations. NWLB Case no.494, 1945 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Clarolyte Plastics. NWLB Case no.380, 1944 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- A. Cohen Brassieres. NWLB Case no.391, 1945 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Cohoes Silk Undergarment. NWLB Case no.221, 1942-1944 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Cohoes Silk Undergarment. NWLB Case no.78, 1942-1944 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Cohen, Friedlander and Martin. NWLB Case no.319, 1944 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- College Clothing Manufacturing Company. NWLB Case no.95, 1943 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Columbia Garment Company. NWLB Case no.40, 1942-1944 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Commercial Dress Company. NWLB Case no.17, 1942-1943 (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Frederic Conde, Inc. NWLB Case no.220, 1943-1945 (Box 2, Folder 23)
- Frederic Conde, Inc. NWLB Case no.485, 1943-1945 (Box 2, Folder 24)
- Coronet Manufacturing Company. NWLB Case no.338, 1944 (Box 2, Folder 25)
- Cotton Garment and Miscellaneous (National). NWLB Case no.232, 1944 (Box 2, Folder 26)
- Cove Dress Company. NWLB Case no.334, 1944 (Box 2, Folder 27)
- Crown Corset. NWLB Case no.449, 1943-1945 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  See also NWLB Case no.214
- Crown Corset. NWLB Case no.214, 1943-1945 (Box 2, Folder 29)
- D. R. Clothing Company, Inc. NWLB Case no.55, 1943 (Box 2, Folder 30)
- Davidson Brothers Corporation. NWLB Case no.406, 1945 (Box 2, Folder 31)
- Davis Square Mattress Company. NWLB Case no.125, 1943-1944 (Box 2, Folder 32)
- Davis Square Mattress Company. NWLB Case no.255, 1943-1944 (Box 2, Folder 33)
- De Garcy Aquilla Company. NWLB Case no.62, 1943 (Box 2, Folder 33a)
- Alfred De Gennaro. NWLB Case no.482, 1943-1945 (Box 2, Folder 34)
- Jacob DeJong, Inc. NWLB Case no.56, 1943 (Box 2, Folder 35)
- Delford Dress Company., 1943 (Box 2, Folder 36)
- A. DePinna and Company. NWLB Case no.126, 1943-1945 (Box 2, Folder 37)
- A. DePinna and Company. NWLB Case no.369, 1943-1945 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  See also NWLB Case no.126
- Derby Sportswear. NWLB Case no.292, 1941-1944 (Box 2, Folder 39)
- Diane Sportswear. NWLB Case no.142, 1943 (Box 2, Folder 40)
- Dick's Dress Company. NWLB Case no.357, 1944 (Box 2, Folder 41)
- Dolores Dress Company. NWLB Case no.256, 1944-1945 (Box 2, Folder 42)
- Dolores Dress Company. NWLB Case no.419, 1944-1945 (Box 2, Folder 43)
- Kay Dunhill, Inc. NWLB Case no.91, 1943-1945 (Box 2, Folder 44)
- Kay Dunhill, Inc. NWLB Case no.208, 1943-1945 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  See also N & B Case no.209
- Kay Dunhill, Inc. NWLB Case no.459, 1943-1945 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  See also NWLB Case no.91 and NWLB Case no.208
- Dutchess Underwear Corporation. NWLB Case no.136, 1943-1945 (Box 2, Folder 47)
- Dutchess Underwear Corporation. NWLB Case no.385, 1943-1945 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  See also NWLB Case no.136
- David Eagle. NWLB Case no.382, 1943-1945 (Box 2, Folder 49)
- Eastern Isles Importing Company. NWLB Case no.178, 1943-1944 (Box 2, Folder 50)
- Eastern Manufacturing Company. NWLB Case no.456b, 1945 (Box 2, Folder 51)
- Easton Dress. NWLB Case no.279, 1944-1945 (Box 2, Folder 52)
- Elias Sportswear Company. NWLB Case no.34, 1942-1943 (Box 2, Folder 53)
- Anne Elliott. NWLB Case no.490 (n.d.) (Box 2, Folder 54)
- Elton Dress. NWLB Case no.143, 1943 (Box 2, Folder 55)
- Empire Sanitary Specialties. NWLB Case no.236, 1943-1944 (Box 2, Folder 56)
- Empire Shield Company. NWLB Case no.235, 1944 (Box 2, Folder 57)
- English Tailor. NWLB Case no.475, 1944-1945 (Box 2, Folder 58)
- Ensig Manufacturing Company. NWLB Case no.187, 1943-1944 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Enterprise and Century Undergarment Company. NWLB Case no.92, 1943-1944 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Enterprise and Century Undergarment Company (South Norwalk). NWLB Case no.108, 1943-1944 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Enterprise and Century Undergarment Company. NWLB Case no.198, 1943-1944 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  See also NWLB Case no.108
- I. Eskin and Son. NWLB Case no.371, 1944-1945 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Essex Undergarment Company. NWLB Case no.74, 1943 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Esskay Manufacturing Company. NWLB Case no.246b, 1944 (Box 3, Folder 6a)
  See also Seven Texas Firms, NWLB Case no.246
- Fashion Dress Company, Inc. NWLB Case no.395, 1943-1945 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Fayette Sportswear Company. NWLB Case no.50, 1941-1943 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- S. Feller and Sons. NWLB Case no.19, 1941-1943 (Box 3, Folder 8a)
- Figure Builder Foundations, Inc. NWLB Case no.438, 1945 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Charles Fiore. NWLB Case no.275, 1944 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Fitwell Underwear Company. NWLB Case no.248, 1936-1944 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- M. W. Flaster Cloak Company, Inc. NWLB Case no.166, 1943 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Flossie Dress Company. NWLB Case no.326, 1943-1945 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  See also NWLB Case no.66 and NWLB Case no.407
- Flossie Dress Company. NWLB Case no.66, 1943-1945 (Box 3, Folder 13a)
  See also NWLB Case no.326 and NWLB Case no.407
- Flossie Dress Company. NWLB Case no.407, 1943-1945 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  See also NWLB Case no.66 and NWLB Case no.326
- Ford Manufacturing Company. NWLB Case no.479, 1943-1945 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Fountain Hill Underwear Mills., 1942-1944 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Fountain Hill Underwear Mills. NWLB Case no.195, 1942-1944 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Fountain Hill Underwear Mills. NWLB Case no.322, 1942-1944 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  See also NWLB Case no.195
- Freeland Dress Company. NWLB Case no.310, 1943-1944 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Friedman Dress. NWLB Case no.120 (n.d.) (Box 3, Folder 19a)
- Kate Friedheim. NWLB Case no.488, 1944-1945 (Box 3, Folder 20)
- Hugo Freund and Son. NWLB Case no.330, 1944 (Box 3, Folder 21)
- Sol Friedman and Son., 1944 (Box 3, Folder 22)
- Fuld and Hatch Knitting Company. NWLB Case no.430, 1945 (Box 3, Folder 23)
- Gamson. NWLB Case no.262, 1944 (Box 3, Folder 24)
- Alex Garafiel, Inc. NWLB Case no.26, 1942 (Box 3, Folder 25)
- Garment Manufacturing. NWLB Case no.316, 1944 (Box 3, Folder 26)
- J. W. Geiger and Company. NWLB Case no.28, 1942-1943 (Box 3, Folder 27)
- General Garment Manufacturing Company, George F. Brasfield., 1943-1944 (Box 3, Folder 28)
- General Textile Mills. NWLB Case no.289, 1943-1944 (Box 3, Folder 29)
- Gene's Dress Shop., 1943 (Box 3, Folder 30)
- Gerson and Kaplan. NWLB Case no.247, 1943-1945 (Box 3, Folder 31)
- Gerson and Kaplan. NWLB Case no.333, 1943-1945 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  See also NWLB Case no.247
- Gerson and Kaplan. NWLB Case no.474, 1943-1945 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  See also NWLB Case no.247 and NWLB Case no.333
- I. Ginsberg and Brothers. NWLB Case no.339, 1943-1945 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  See also NWLB Case no.116
- I. Ginsberg and Brothers. NWLB Case no.116, 1943-1945 (Box 3, Folder 34a)
- I. Ginsberg and Brothers. NWLB Case no.416, 1943-1945 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  See also NWLB Case no.116 and NWLB Case no.339
- Globe Underwear. NWLB Case no.396, 1944-1945 (Box 3, Folder 36)
- Globe Underwear. NWLB Case no.87, 1944-1945 (Box 3, Folder 36a)
- Goetz and Kleeban. NWLB Case no.348, 1944-1945 (Box 3, Folder 37)
- Goldman Company. NWLB Case no.377, 1945 (Box 3, Folder 38)
- Gordon Brothers Manufacturing Company. NWLB Case no.22, 1942 (Box 3, Folder 38a)
- Graceform Camlin. NWLB Case no.251, 1944 (Box 3, Folder 39)
- Gracette. NWLB Case no.344, 1944 (Box 3, Folder 40)
- L. N. Gross Company. NWLB Case no.24, 1941-1942 (Box 3, Folder 41)
- Grove Manufacturing. NWLB Case no.70, 1943 (Box 3, Folder 42)
- Angelo Guttadaro. NWLB Case no.168, 1942-1943 (Box 3, Folder 43)
- Haber Lingerie, Inc., 1941-1943 (Box 3, Folder 44)
- R. Hanschrow. NWLB Case no.454, 1945 (Box 3, Folder 45)
- Harris Dress Company. NWLB Case no.81, 1943 (Box 3, Folder 46)
- Harris Raincoat Company. NWLB Case no.94, 1942-1944 (Box 3, Folder 47)
- Harris Raincoat Company. NWLB Case no.148, 1942-1944 (Box 3, Folder 48)
- Harris Raincoat Company. NWLB Case no.264, 1942-1944 (Box 3, Folder 49)
  See also NWLB Case no.94 and NWLB Case no.148
- Hazleton -McAdoo. NWLB Case no.426, 1945 (Box 3, Folder 50)
  See also NWLB Case no.283
- Hazleton Sportswear. NWLB Case no.283, 1944 (Box 3, Folder 51)
- Hebron Manufacturing Company. NWLB Case no.180, 1943-1944 (Box 3, Folder 52)
- Hebron Manufacturing Company - Hebron, MD. NWLB Case no.317, 1943-1944 (Box 3, Folder 53)
- Hebron Manufacturing Company - Sharpton, MD. NWLB Case no.318, 1943-1944 (Box 3, Folder 54)
- Hill Button (Plastics) Company. NWLB Case no.392, 1944 (Box 3, Folder 55)
- S. P. Hirshberg (Best Maid). NWLB Case no.290, 1944 (Box 3, Folder 56)
- S. L. Hoffman. NWLB Case no.455, 1943-1945 (Box 3, Folder 57)
- Home Manufacturing Company. NWLB Case no.3, 1943 (Box 3, Folder 57a)
- Hoosick Falls Undergarment. NWLB Case no.117, 1942-1943 (Box 3, Folder 58)
- Howard Garments, Inc. NWLB Case no.6, 1942-1943 (Box 3, Folder 59)
- E. Heubner and Sons. NWLB Case no.362, 1944 (Box 3, Folder 60)
- Hygiene Shower Curtain Manufacturing Company. NWLB Case no.204, 1943-1944 (Box 3, Folder 61)
- Hygiene Shower Curtain Manufacturing Company. NWLB Case no.354, 1943-1944 (Box 3, Folder 62)
  See also NWLB Case no.204 and NWLB Case no.286
- Hygiene Shower Curtain Manufacturing Company. NWLB Case no.286, 1943-1944 (Box 3, Folder 63)
  See also NWLB Case no.204
- Imperial Coat Company. NWLB Case no.313, 1944 (Box 3, Folder 64)
- Imperial Manufacturing Company. NWLB Case no.250, 1944-1945 (Box 3, Folder 65)
- Imperial Manufacturing Company. NWLB Case no.393, 1944-1945 (Box 3, Folder 66)
  See also NWLB Case no.250 and NWLB Case no.374
- Imperial Manufacturing Company. NWLB Case no.374, 1944-1945 (Box 3, Folder 67)
  See also NWLB Case no.250
- Inwood Manufacturing Company. NWLB Case no.276, 1944-1945 (Box 3, Folder 68)
- Island Dress Company. NWLB Case no.374, 1944 (Box 3, Folder 69)
- J and L Dress Company. NWLB Case no.350, 1944 (Box 3, Folder 70)
- Jacobs, Grossman and Rosenberg. NWLB Case no.291, 1944 (Box 3, Folder 71)
- M. Janowitch and Sons. NWLB Case no.403, 1945 (Box 3, Folder 72)
- Japo Button Works, Inc. NWLB Case no.184, 1943-1944 (Box 3, Folder 73)
- Jennie Dress Company. NWLB Case no.12, 1942-1943 (Box 3, Folder 74)
- Jessup Company, Inc. NWLB Case no.361, 1945 (Box 3, Folder 75)
- Joniel Sportswear Company. NWLB Case no.2666, 1943-1944 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Joselli. NWLB Case no.293, 1943-1944 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Juvenile Manufacturing Company. NWLB Case no.246-C, 1944-1945 (Box 4, Folder 2a)
- Juvenile Manufacturing Company., 1944-1945 (Box 4, Folder 2b)
- Kamore Robe. NWLB Case no.76, 1941-1943 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Kanner Dress Company. NWLB Case no.5, 1943 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Kapinsky and Santora. NWLB Case no.418, 1945 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Kastuck and Company. NWLB Case no.269, 1944 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Kay-Andrews Company. NWLB Case no.4, 1941-1943 (Box 4, Folder 6a)
- Kay-Andrews Company. NWLB Case no.179, 1941-1943 (Box 4, Folder 6b)
  See also NWLB Case no.4
- Keansburg Garment. NWLB Case no.114, 1941-1943 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Kearney Sportswear, Inc. NWLB Case no.54, 1943 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Kehr Edelman. NWLB Case no.161, 1942-1945 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Kehr Edelman. NWLB Case no.428, 1942-1945 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  See also NWLB Case no. 161
- Klein. NWLB Case no.185, 1941-1944 (Box 4, Folder 11)